{
    "subject": "resource/Naoum_Aronson",
    "predicate": "property/hasPhotoCollection",
    "object": "http://wifo5-03.informatik.uni-mannheim.de/flickrwrappr/photos/Naoum_Aronson",
    "human_readable": "Naoum Aronson has a photo collection.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9713530540466309,
            "question": "Is Naoum Aronson a collector?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8836914300918579,
            "question": "What kind of collection does Naoum Aronson possess?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.838766872882843,
            "question": "What does Naoum Aronson have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8362924456596375,
            "question": "Does Naoum Aronson collect anything?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8070639967918396,
            "question": "What type of collection does Naoum Aronson own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7255223989486694,
            "question": "What belongs to Naoum Aronson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7008537650108337,
            "question": "What is Naoum Aronson known for having?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6935029029846191,
            "question": "What item is associated with Naoum Aronson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.547417938709259,
            "question": "What is Naoum Aronson's hobby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5398845076560974,
            "question": "What does Naoum Aronson curate?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Naoum Aronson has a photo collection.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1620_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Naoum Aronson's hobby?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1620_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What item is associated with Naoum Aronson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1620_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Naoum Aronson known for having?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1620_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1620_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention anything about Naoum Aronson having a photo collection. The information in the documents is related to his career as a sculptor, his works, and his life events, but there is no reference to any photo collection belonging to him."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}